Subhajit Chakraborty

Full-Stack Data Engineer

Worked as a Software Implementation Engineer at BuziBrAIns, Full Stack Developer at Encoders Unlimited, and BCA student with various skill sets covering Front-End, Back-End and database technologies. Proficient in JAVA, Python also data analysis & visualization skills, and well-versed in Web technologies like HTML, BootStrap CSS, and ReactJS. Experienced in database design and management.



xc801377@gmail.com

9 West Bengal, Jalpaiguri, India

github.com/SubhajitChakrabort

3768659911

in linkedin.com/in/https://www.linked.com/in/subhajitchakraborty-774904235

EDUCATION

BCA

Siliguri Institute of Technology

08/2021 - Present 8.29 CGPA

12th

Jalpaiguri Zilla School

05/2020 - 06/2021 8.25 CGPA

10th

Fanindradeb Institution

01/2018 - 06/2019 7.37 CGPA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full stack developer Encoders Unlimited

11/2023 - 02/2024 Software Company

Software Implementation Engineer BuziBrAIns

02/2024 - 03/2024 Software Company

SKILLS

HTML BootStrap CSS MERN Stack

Python

MySQL

ata Analytics Java

REST API Automation

PROJECTS

Doctor Appointment App (10/2023 - 11/2023)

 Doctor can add, user authentication, admin function and doctor booking system and doctor & user can be both by admin that's all done using MERN STACK

Ecommerce App (11/2023 - 12/2023)

 Full stack Ecommerce app using MERN STACK where we can do user admin performance, product add, orders process, payment process for the payment process I have used braintree

Covid-19 Data Analysis (02/2024 - 02/2024)

 Using Python, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Seaborn, MS Excel & MS PowerBI

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency

Bengali

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Cricket